So how to print a double link at last?
We have three nodes here, they have middle and last and we need to connect them by and see how to print
them accordingly.
So struck note them I have created in a flash or a pointer called TAM.
Now its reference is the same as the hat print f normal traversal.
So we are now making and printing the double link list as a normal from the hat to the tail.
While stamp does not equal to none.
Move the cursor and attempt equal to the data.
Print that stamp.
Print the data inside the temp and put equal stamp the next.
So every time you make this little while you are iterating just to print the data that it is contained
inside the node and traverse that to the next note by making stamp equal, stamp the next or moving
the cursor from them to stamp next every time until reaching stamp equal to null.
This is the linkage between the hat middle and the last.
And we have created this habit, moving it to the middle.
Getting that the data from it and moving the last, getting the data from it, while stamp dot next
is equal or while temp equal to null because we are referencing to null.
OK, you see guys that had this their Francine now to the null.
The next to last is null.
So it's a break from loop and print out the result 100 to 103 Humphrey.
Now how to print that W linked list reversely if we need to print the double link at list from the last
to the head.
How to do that, we start by struck note temp.
Again, we created temp called equal to had in the same way.
And this reference will start from the last.
How to start from less the same way temp does not equal to known print after attempt to get data.
So we need to get to get data and temp equals temp of previous because this is a list of doubly linked
list.
We know that it's a reference.
OK, so we know it's previous.
Therefore, we start from the last the middle and had.
OK, so we are moving the temp.
The temp.
By changing it from Tampa to Tampa, the previous this is that rift between the printing doubly linked
list like in normal traversal or reversal reversing manner.
OK.
It's very simple.
This is the way how to.